# SILJE AVENA ANGELVIK

+47 957 30 677 angelviksilje@gmail.com

Fæsteråsen 332 Bergen, Hordaland 5184

### **Profile**

Hello, my name is Silje, I am 27 years old and I'm a full-time student at Noroff Vocational School in Bergen, currently at my second and last year.

I started my web-development journey in 2019 joining a web development course for beginners. I thought it was very exciting and enjoyable. I quickly found out how many challenges it would offer me, so I knew that when I finished the course in a year, I wanted to continue on this path to learn more.

The decision I made back in 2019, has led me here, today, writing my CV. Whoever reads this will have a different today than the day I call today, and my today is when I was writing this CV, is January 1st 2023.

## **Experience**

Shop Assistant, Rema 1000; Kleppestø — 2015-2016 Pre School Assistant, Fana Outdoor Kindergarten; Fana — 2016-2019 Course Participant, ALF AS; Bergen — 2019-2020

#### Education

Bjørgvin High School, Bergen - General Studies, 2011-2013 Møre Folk High School, Ørsta - Extreme Sport, 2013-2014 Olsvikåsen High School, Bergen - General Studies, 2013-2014 Noroff University College, Bergen - Front-End Development, 2020-2023

### **Skills**

A loyal and daily user of Google! HTML5, CSS, Bootstrap, Tailwind, SASS, JavaScript, JSON, React, E2E-testing, Unit-Testing, GitHub, Git, Vite, Webpack, WordPress, Netlify.